Hiu Mei Fu

UX / UI Designer

Motivated UI/UX designer with a combination of skills in product design, computer science, and other related fields. Skilled in creating user-friendly experience, and well-versed in coding. Known for being self-initiative, well-organized, and a strong collaborator.

North York, CA +1 (437) 552-0215 meifu.wk@gmail.com https://meifuux.github.io/

Eligible holder of Open Work Permit Available immediately

EXPERIENCE

Orange Data Limited — UX/UI & Graphic Designer

Mar 2022 - Nov 2022, Hong Kong | Dec 2022 - Present, Remote

Capstone Project - Design interface for 'World Cup' gamemode for World Entertainment casino

- Designs various product interfaces, including web and mobile
- Creates user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and mockups
- Collaborates with cross-functional teams to implementation user-centered designs
- Creates marketing and promotional materials

Semeiotics Group (Asia) Limited— Junior Web Designer

Mar 2021 - Nov 2021, Hong Kong

- Designed the layout, color scheme, and overall appearance of a website
- Implemented the design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & CMS

SenMedia Limited — *Technical Artist*

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022, Freelance

Capstone Project - Acted as leader for government website revamp. Optimized information architecture

- Created visually appealing and engaging designs that meet the needs of projects, such as website, installations mobile games
- Collaborated with various teams, including developers, project managers, stakeholders and clients

EDUCATION

City University Of Hong Kong, Hong Kong — Bachelor Of Science In Creative Media

Aug 2015 - Oct 2019

Focus: UX/UI Design | Computer Science | Creative Media

SKILLS

UX Design / Research

Design Persona & Scenario
Information Architecture
Interaction & Visual Design
Wireframing & Prototyping
Journey Map
Data Visualization
Contextual Inquiry Interview
Survey Affinity Analysis
Competitive Analysis

TOOLKIT

Design Tools

Usability Testing

Figma, Sketch, Adobe suits (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects etc.)

Programing Tools

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL

CERTIFICATIONS

Google UX Design Professional Certificate, Coursera | Google

Credential ID: 9JDNBHW3KQ9P

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing, Google

Credential ID: 3EH DR6 67L

AWARDS

Hong Kong ICT Awards 2020 - Certification of Merit, Student Innovation

LANGUAGES

English, Mandarin, Cantonese - Fluent Japanese - Intermediate